[GROANS]
[CONTINUES GROANING]
(Leonard:)Problem?
- This is Thai food.
- Here we go.
(Sheldon:)We don't have Thai food on Thursday.
We have pizza on Thursday.
(Leonard:)Yes, but we all agreed
the third Thursday of every month...
(Leonard:)...would be
Anything Can Happen Thursday.
(Sheldon:)The news didn't reach
my digestive system which, when startled...
(Sheldon:)...has its own version
of Anything Can Happen Thursday.
(Howard:)The whole idea behind
Anything Can Happen Thursday...
(Howard:)...is to get out of this rut
we've been in.
(Sheldon:)Rut? I think you mean consistency.
(Sheldon:)And if we're going to abandon that,
why even call it Thursday?
Let's call it "Quonko Day" and divide it
into 29 hours of 17 minutes a piece...
(Sheldon:)...and celebrate it by sacrificing a goat
to the mighty god Ra.
(Raj:)I could go for some goat.